const questions = [
	{
		question: "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?",
		answers: [
			"The Millennium Falcon",
			"The Death Star",
			"The Enterprise",
			"The Tardis"
		],
		correctAnswer: "The Millennium Falcon"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Chewbacca is from?",
		answers: ["Kashyyyk", "Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor"],
		correctAnswer: "Kashyyyk"
	},
	{
		question:
			"What is the name of the bounty hunter that captures Han Solo?",
		answers: ["Boba Fett", "Jango Fett", "Dengar", "Bossk"],
		correctAnswer: "Boba Fett"
	},
	{
		question: "Who is Luke and Leia's mother?",
		answers: ["Padme Amidala", "Shmi Skywalker", "Beru Lars", "Mon Mothma"],
		correctAnswer: "Padme Amidala"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Luke is from?",
		answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Tatooine"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Obi-Wan Kenobi is from?",
		answers: ["Stewjon", "Tatooine", "Coruscant", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Stewjon"
	},
	{
		question:
			"What is the name of the planet that Anakin Skywalker is from?",
		answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Tatooine"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Yoda is from?",
		answers: ["Dagobah", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Dagobah"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Darth Maul is from?",
		answers: ["Dathomir", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Dathomir"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Darth Vader is from?",
		answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Tatooine"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Count Dooku is from?",
		answers: ["Serenno", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Serenno"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Jabba the Hutt is from?",
		answers: ["Nal Hutta", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Nal Hutta"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Boba Fett is from?",
		answers: ["Kamino", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Kamino"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Jango Fett is from?",
		answers: ["Concord Dawn", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Concord Dawn"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Mace Windu is from?",
		answers: ["Haruun Kal", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Haruun Kal"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Qui-Gon Jinn is from?",
		answers: ["Coruscant", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Coruscant"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Padme Amidala is from?",
		answers: ["Naboo", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Naboo"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Jar Jar Binks is from?",
		answers: ["Naboo", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Naboo"
	},
	{
		question:
			"What is the name of the planet that General Grievous is from?",
		answers: ["Kalee", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Kalee"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that General Hux is from?",
		answers: ["Aridus", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Aridus"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Kylo Ren is from?",
		answers: ["Chandrila", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Chandrila"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Poe Dameron is from?",
		answers: ["Yavin 4", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Yavin 4"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Finn is from?",
		answers: ["Jakku", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Jakku"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Rey is from?",
		answers: ["Jakku", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Jakku"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Captain Phasma is from?",
		answers: ["Parnassos", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Parnassos"
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the planet that Snoke is from?",
		answers: ["Unknown Regions", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
		correctAnswer: "Unknown Regions"
	}
];

export default questions;
